# Rutunjay Shriram Jagtap () Featured

Software Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Support, Project Management, Change Management, Defect Management, Quality Management, Requirement Gathering, Core Java, Bootstrap, Hibernate, Eclipse, MySQL, HTML, CSS,



Current Designation: Software Developer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Infraroot Solutions LLP Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Mechanical]

Pref. Location: Pune

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Core Java, Advanced Java, Spring, Hibernate, Spring Mvc, vuejs, Node.Js, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript,

Bootstrap, UI Development, Software Development,

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

### **Summary**

Seeking position in an organization where there is an opportunity to exhibit, strengthen and enhance skills by utilizing myself as a resource for all kinds of challenging jobs and keeping my goals in tandem with those of organization.

Having around 2 Years of IT experience and technical proficiency in Java/J2EE technologies.

Strong exposure in development of Web Applications using technologies like Core Java,

Servlets, JSP, and Frame Works like Spring MVC, Hibernate.

Experience in developing and deploying applications in Apache Tomcat servers.

Good Knowledge at OOPS Concepts.

Experience in build tools like Eclipse, Visual Studio.

Experience in different stages of software development life cycle (SDLC).

Ability to work on individually if needed and clearly communicate issues to development team and management.

### **Work Experience**

# Infraroot Solutions LLP as Software Developer

Aug 2018 to Till Date

Company

Infraroot Solutions Pvt. Ltd Project-1

National Delhi Muncipal Corporation (Delhi) Duration

November 2018-July 2019 Technology/Tools used

Spring & Hibernate 3.0, HTML/CSS, Eclipse, Visual Studio.

Databases:

MySQL Responsibilities:

- \* Responsible for coding of DAO classes using Spring with hibernate.
- \* Implementing Business logic.
- \* Involved in Functional Testing.
- \* Developing at Client side validations using Spring validator
- \* Developing frontend web application.

Description

National Delhi Muncipal Corporation is a government hospital project which was in Delhi. As a part of this web application user can maintain government records and issue birth certificates, death certificates. Also it maintains records of patients in hospitals as well.

Project-2

Tithee Duration

August 2019-July 2020 Technology/Tools used

HTML/CSS, Vue JS, Node JS, Visual Studio, POSTMAN

Databases:

MySQL Responsibilities:

- \* Developing frontend web application with HTML/CSS.
- \* Conversion of developed frontend web application into Vue JS.
- \* Responsible for creating APIs for client application.
- \* Implementation of APIs.
- \* Updating client time to time about the project.
- \* Implementation of feedback received from client.

Description

Tithee is a due date reminder web application of various taxes. Through this user can subscribe various plans and get time to time reminder about the taxes.

Project-3

Cloudstack API Duration

August 2020-on going Technology/Tools used

Node JS, Visual Studio, command prompt

Responsibilities:

\* Testing of various apis and displaying the result with HTML

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from Sinhgad Institute of Technology and Science, Pune in 2018

#### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Core Java ,Advance Java, MySQL			
Spring, Hibernate, REST web services.			
Apache Tomcat, Node JS, Windows			
HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Vue Js			
Eclipse IDE, Visual Studio, POSTMAN			

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time